Curriculum Vitae

SUMMARY

Over 25 years of experience with automation, test systems, project management, data acquisition, lean processes, calibration, and software development. Focus has been on sustaining, creating, and maintaining test systems, including software, of all forms used in final quality control and engineering solutions worldwide.

The most successful solutions come from an open mind towards the issues at hand and listening to opposing or different ideas with a receptive, respectful attitude.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Accurate Technology and Test Automation LLC (ATTA), Tulsa, OK, USA

Founder and Managing Director, April 2017 to Present

- Created Python based software solution that communicates with Allen Bradley *Logix devices using a RESTful API. Designed to be extensible for additional industrial protocols.
- Worked with MySQL, Redis, JSON, HTML5, Javascript, and Flask to build web app.
- Deployment of software using Ansible on AWS and local thin server.
- Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) software solutions for data acquisition, aggregation, analysis, and machine control.
- Developed standardized Modular Control System (MCS) designed for flexibility and easy installation of test systems used in the field.
- Software and hardware solutions increased productivity for one customer by 60% and paid for itself in less than 6 months on the first installed test system.
- Provided remote support for customers with IT issues related to test systems.
- Worked with valve company to improve performance of newly designed control valve.

Contractor, Singapore

Trainer, Jan 16 to Jan 26, 2017

- Taught class on calibration, troubleshooting, and service of Electrical Submersible Pump test systems.
- Trained people on the proper technique to train new people to work with these test systems, "train the trainer".
- Worked with a team to help plan for the future of the customers test systems and service centers.

Curriculum Vitae

Schlumberger, Bartlesville, OK, USA

Electrical Engineer, HPS Group, 2015 to 2016

Designed and sustained electrical systems for Schlumberger Horizontal Pump System product line.

- Wrote Python programs to automate documentation creation. Cut time required to create data books by 50%
- Automated Excel spreadsheets using VBA macros.
- Created and updated AutoCAD electrical drawings.
- Modified and reviewed P&ID drawings.
- Specified new electrical instrumentation and automation components for product design.
- Oversaw root cause analysis of electrical production issues.

Schlumberger, Bartlesville, OK, USA

Controls Engineer, Service Center Tooling, 2013 to 2015

Designed and sustained control systems and electrical systems for the Schlumberger test system product line. This included Pump Test, Motor Test, Cable Test, and Protector Test.

- Programmed PLC and HMI for test systems.
- Streamlined automated test systems designs using new technology.
- Specified instrumentation for test systems.
- Developed next generation control system for test equipment.
- Automated test system controls and operation expert.
- Supported technical issues and quality control of test system manufacturing.
- Created BOM's for new test system developments and previous system upgrades.

ART-C Support Engineer, Assembly Repair and Test Center (ART-C) Support, 2006 to 2013 Serviced, upgraded, installed, and certified test systems at over 30 locations worldwide.

- Managed installation of high spec data acquisition system for a \$1.5 Billion Petrobras project.
- Team member for design of test system to meet Petrobras requirements.
- Specified instrumentation for vibration acquisition systems.
- Developed budgets for test system improvement projects.
- Coordinated shipment of calibration equipment and required visas for travel.
- Trained personnel to calibrate and certify test systems.
- Mentored for calibration, certification, installation, and troubleshooting.
- Diagnosed and repaired automated test systems.
- Worked with vendors and outside contractors to complete tasks.
- Programmed PLC and HMI for test systems.
- Created BOM's for new test system developments and previous system upgrades.
- Installed and setup VSD's as a test system component.
- System integrator of several dissimilar components.
- Extensive knowledge on multiple sensors, analog signals, and communication protocol.

Curriculum Vitae

Electronic Technician, Maintenance, 2001 to 2006

Troubleshoot, repair, and maintain various automated machines.

- Implemented maintenance plan for nearly 100 environmental control units in the plant.
- Produced easily understood procedures for common processes in maintenance.
- General troubleshooting, repair, and maintenance of a variety of automated machines.

Port City Plate, Tulsa, OK, USA

Electronic Technician, Maintenance, 1999 to 2001

Troubleshoot, repair, and maintain various automated machines.

Troubleshooting and repair of plasma and gas torch automated cutting machines.

McBroom Industrial, Indianapolis, IN, USA

Field Service/Servo/Precision Spindle Repair Technician, 1994 to 1999

Troubleshot, repair, and maintain various automated machines, servo systems, and high speed precision spindle motors.

- Reverse engineered and determined repair procedures for servo motors from several different manufacturers.
- Development of servo load test system for McBroom Industrial.
- Set up VSD and CNC controllers for the purpose of testing servo systems in final quality control test.
- Troubleshooting and repair of automated machines and test systems used at the customer's facilities. Including Borg Warner, GM Truck and Bus, Bemis, and many other industries in the Indianapolis area.
- Training of new personnel on processes used at McBroom Industrial.

European Tanning Systems(ETS), Indianapolis, IN, USA

Field Service/Phone Support Repair Technician, 1993 to 1994

Troubleshot, repair, and provide on site service of tanning systems.

- Provide phone support of tanning systems sold by ETS
- On site support and repair of tanning systems

Curriculum Vitae

EDUCATION / TRAINING

Associates, Electronics Engineering Technology, ITT Technical Institute
ControlLogix/Studio 5000 Logix Designer, Rockwell Automation

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming: Python, HTML, Javascript, JSON, RESTful API, Flask, Redis, MySQL, Git, PLC Ladder, HMI

Industrial Hardware: Allen Bradley, Schneider Electric, Modicon, Magelis, Emerson, Fanuc, Allen Bradley, Mazak, National Instruments, Kollmorgen

Software: Studio 5000, Unity Pro, TwidoSuite, Vijeo, PL7, National Instruments, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Power Point, Microsoft Word, AutoCAD

Operating Systems: Windows XP, Windows 7, Windows 8, Windows 10, Ubuntu Linux desktop and server.

Industrial Protocols: RS485 ASCII, RS485 Modbus, RS232 Serial, CAN bus, Modbus TCP/IP, HART protocol

CONTACT

Cell: 918-766-6102

Email: josie.peacock0130@gmail.com

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/josiebpeacock

ATS Optimization:

Accurate, Actuators, Advanced, Analytical, Analyze, Automation, Budget,

CAD, Compliance, Consulting, Controls Engineer, Corrective, Customer

Requirements, Develop, Documentation, Effective, Engineering

Drawings, Engineers, English, Facility, Flow, Fluid, Implement, Implementation,

Instrumentation, Investigation, Investigations, Interface, ISO, Lead, Lean

Manufacturing, Machinery, Measurement, Meeting Facilitation, MOC, New

Designs, Performance, Problems, Process Improvement, Process, Programmable Logic

Controllers, Prototyping, Quality Management System,

Regulatory, Safety, Scada, Sensors, Specification, Specifications, Teams, Tech, Technical

Guidance, Technical Knowledge, Technical

Writing, Testing, Training, Understanding, Visual, Wiring, MySQL, Redis, Flask